{
    "question": [
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In the 1968 Cartoon Show &quot;Wacky Races&quot; what was the name of cavemen duo who rode in The Boulder Mobile?",
            "correct_answer": "The Slag Brothers",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Slate Brothers",
                "The Rock Brothers",
                "The Stone Brothers"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In &quot;Rick and Morty&quot;, from which dimension do Rick and Morty originate from?",
            "correct_answer": "C-137",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "J1977",
                "C-136",
                "C500-a"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "Which of the following films was Don Bluth both the writer, director, and producer for?",
            "correct_answer": "All Dogs Go To Heaven",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Titan A.E.",
                "Anastasia",
                "The Land Before Time"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "What was Maggie Simpson&#039;s first canonical word, not including the Tracey Ullman shorts?",
            "correct_answer": "Daddy.",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Sequel?",
                "Ja!",
                "Rusty!"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "Townsend Coleman provided the voice for which turtle in the original 1987 series of &quot;Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Michelangelo",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Leonardo",
                "Donatello",
                "Raphael"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "Benny, Brain, Fancy-Fancy, Spook and Choo-Choo were known associates of what Hanna Barbera cartoon character?",
            "correct_answer": "Top Cat",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Yogi Bear",
                "Snagglepuss",
                "Scooby-Doo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "What was the name of Jonny&#039;s pet dog in The Adventures of Jonny Quest?",
            "correct_answer": "Bandit",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lucky",
                "Rocky",
                "Max"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "What town was &quot;Springfield&quot; from &quot;The Simpsons&quot; originally named after?",
            "correct_answer": "Springfield, Oregon",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Springfield, Missouri",
                "Springfield, Illinois",
                "Springfield, Massachusetts"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In &quot;Gravity Falls&quot;, how much does Waddles weigh when Mable wins him in &quot;The Time Traveler&#039;s Pig&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "15 pounds",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "20 pounds",
                "10 pounds",
                "30 pounds"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In &quot;Gravity Falls&quot;, what does Quentin Trembley do when he is driven out from the White House?",
            "correct_answer": "Eat a salamander and jump out the window.",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Leave in peace.",
                "Jump out the window.",
                "Release 1,000 captive salamanders into the white house."
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In &quot;Gravity Falls&quot;, the character Bill Cipher remarks that &quot;the universe is what?&quot;",
            "correct_answer": "A hologram ",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "An illusion ",
                "A simulation",
                "Corrupting"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "Who voice acted the character Hiccup in the movie &quot;How to Train Your Dragon&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Jay Baruchel",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jack Brauchel",
                "John Powell",
                "Gerard Butler"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In the TV show &quot;Rick and Morty&quot;, Rick uses the catchphrase &quot;Wubba Lubba Dub Dub&quot;, which means what in Birdperson?",
            "correct_answer": "I am in great pain, please help me.",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "I pray that my life ends soon.",
                "Lets get this party started!",
                "I am suffering, please help me."
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In the &quot;Star Wars&quot; universe, what species is Grand Admiral Thrawn?",
            "correct_answer": "Chiss",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Gungans",
                "Pantorans",
                "Twi&#039;lek"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In the 1969 Cartoon show &quot;Dastardly and Muttley in Their Flying Machines&quot;, which were NOT one of the lyrics in the opening theme?",
            "correct_answer": "Stab him",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Nab him",
                "Jab him",
                "Tab him"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "In the web-comic Homestuck, what is the name of the game the 4 kids play?",
            "correct_answer": "Sburb",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Homesick",
                "Husslie",
                "Hiveswap"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "Who played Stan&#039;s dog in the South Park episode &quot;Big Gay Al&#039;s Big Gay Boat Ride&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "George Clooney",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jay Leno",
                "Matt Stone",
                "Robert Smith"
            ]
        }
    ]
}